{
  "posts": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "json-server",
      "author": "typicode"
    }
  ],
  "comments": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "body": "some comment",
      "postId": 1
    }
  ],
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": 9,
      "name": "kkkk",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Test Question 2",
          "answer": "Test Answer 2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "name": "testni quz",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "your last name",
          "answer": "adilovic"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "your town",
          "answer": "bihac"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Test Question 2",
          "answer": "Test Answer 2"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "your name",
          "answer": "aki"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "boby",
          "answer": "boy"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "name": "starac",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "starac question 1",
          "answer": "starac answer 1"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "starac question 2",
          "answer": "starac answer 2"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Test Question 2",
          "answer": "Test Answer 2"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "your town",
          "answer": "bihac"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "name": "fdsfds",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "name": "hello",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Test Question 2",
          "answer": "Test Answer 2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "name": "vvv",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "name": "ggg",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "name": "fdgdgf",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "name": "fsdfsd",
      "questions": []
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "name": "gfgd",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Test Question 2",
          "answer": "Test Answer 2"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "your name",
          "answer": "aki"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "name": "rtyy",
      "questions": []
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
      "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Test Question 2",
      "answer": "Test Answer 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "your name",
      "answer": "aki"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "your last name",
      "answer": "adilovic"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "your town",
      "answer": "bihac"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "boby",
      "answer": "boy"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "starac question 1",
      "answer": "starac answer 1"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "starac question 2",
      "answer": "starac answer 2"
    }
  ],
  "profile": {
    "name": "typicode"
  }
}